Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- United States General Accounting Office - Werneke, Diane., Publication (Box 26)
  - Voos, Paula B., and Tsan-Yuang Cheng, "What Do Managers Mean by Cooperative Labor Relations?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: What Do Managers Mean by Cooperative Labor Relations?, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)
      Author: Paula B. Voos and Tsan-Yuang Cheng
  - Voydanoff, Patriciea, Highlights of the Literature: The Implications of Work-Family Relationships for Productivity, Publication (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: The Implications of Work-Family Relationships for Productivity, 1980; Publication (Box 26, Folder 35)
      Author: Patricia Voydanoff
  - Wachter, Janet T., "Remarks", Publication (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 36)
      Author: Janet T. Wachter
  - Wacker, Gerald and Nadler, Gerald, "7 Myths About the Quality of Working Life", Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: 7 Myths About Quality of Working Life, 1980; Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
      Author: Gerald Wacker and Gerald Nadler
  - Wada, Sadami, "Sony Keeps High Quality and Productivity in the United States", Publication (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Sony Keeps High Quality and Productivity in the United States, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 38)
      Author: Sadami Wada
  - Wagel, William H., "Opening the Door to Employee Participation", Publication (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Opening the Door to Employee Participation, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 39)
      Author: William H. Wagel
  - Wakin, Edward, "Quality Circles: Management Magic?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles: Management Magic?, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
      Author: Edward Wakin
  - Wakin, Ed, "Quality of Work Life: Labor's Love Found", Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Quality of Work Life: Labor's Love Found, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
      Author: Ed Wakin
  - Walker, Cynthia K. "Stressed to Kill", Publication (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Stressed to Kill, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 42)
      Author: Cynthia K. Walker
  - Walker, Kenneth F., "Workers' Participation in Management--Problems, Practice and Prospects", Publication (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Workers' Participation in Management- Problems, Practice and Prospects, 1977; Publication (Box 26, Folder 43)
      Author: Kenneth F. Walker
  - Wall, Toby D., Paul R. Jackson, and Keith Davids, "Operator Work Design and Robotics System Performance: A Serendipitous Field Study", Publication (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Operator Work Design and Robotics System Performance: A Serendipitous Field Study, 1992; Publication (Box 26, Folder 44)
      Author: Toby D. Wall, Paul R. Jackson, Keith Davids
  - Wallace, F. Blake, "Are Incentives Right for U.S. White Collar Organizations", Publication (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Are Incentives Right for U.S. White Collar Organizations, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 45)
      Author: F. Blake Wallace
  - Wallace, Mark J., Rewards and Renewal: America's Search for Competitive Advantage Through Alternative Pay Strategies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Rewards and Renewal: America's Search for Competitive Advantage Through Alternative Pay Strategies, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 46)
      Author: Marc J. Wallace
  - Walsh, J. Michael and Stephen C. Yohay, Drug and Alcohol Abuse in the Workplace: A Guide to the Issues, Publication (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Drug and Alcohol Abuse in the Workplace: A Guide to the Issues, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 47)
      Author: J. Michael Walsh and Stephen C. Yohay
  - Walt, Harold R., "Toward 2000", Publication (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Toward 2000, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 48)
      Author: Harold R. Walt
  - Walton, Richard E., and Robert B. McKersie, "Managing Labor Relations and the Introduction of New Technology", Publication (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Managing Labor Relations and the Introduction of New Technology, 1988; Publication (Box 26, Folder 49)
      Author: Richard E. Walton and Robert B. McKersie
  - Walton, Richard E., "From Control to Commitment: Transforming Work Force Management in the United States", Publication (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: From Control to Commitment: Transforming Work Force Management in the United States, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 50)
      Author: Richard E. Walton
  - Walton, Richard, "How Can Worker and Union Commitment be Encouraged to Contribute to Industrial Competitiveness", Publication (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: How Can Worker and Union Commitment be Encouraged to Contribute to Industrial Competitiveness, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 51)
      Author: Richard Walton
  - Walton, Richard E., "How to Counter Alienation in the Plant", Publication (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: How to Counter Alienation in the Plant, 1972; Publication (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Walton, Richard E., "New Information Technology: Organizational Problem or Opportunity?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: New Information Technology: Organizational Problem or Opportunity?, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Walton, Richard E., "New Work Technology and Its Work Force Implications: Union and Management Approaches", Publication (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: New Work Technology and its Work Force Implications: Union and Management Approaches, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Walton, Richard E., and Gerald I. Susman, "People Policies for the New Machines", Publication (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: People Policies for the New Machines, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Walton, Richard E., "Social Choice in the Development of Advanced Technology", Publication (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Social Choice in the Development of Advanced Information Technology, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Walton, Richard E., "Social Choice in the Development of Advanced Information Technology in Rhodes and Wield (eds.)", Publication (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Social Choice in the Development of Advanced Information Technology, 1985; Publication (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Walton, Richard E., "The Diffusion of New Work Structures: Explaining Why Success Didn't Take", Publication (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: The Diffusion of New Work Structures: Explaining Why Success Didn't Take, 1975; Publication (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Walton, Richard E., "The Topeka Work System: Optimistic Visions, Pessimistic Hypothesis and Reality", Publication (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: The Topeka Work System: Optimistic Vissions, Pessimistic Hypothesis and Reality, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Ward, Dan L., "The Cost Implications of a No-Layoff Policy", Publication (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: The Cost Implications of a No-Layoff Policy, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 60)
      Author: Dan L. Ward
  - Warner, David. "Labor Targets the States", Publication (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Corporatism, Participation and Society, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 61)
      Author: Malcolm Warner
  - Warner, Malcolm, "Corporatism, Participation and Society", Publication (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Work Democracy: Towards a Three-Dimensional Approach, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Warner, Malcolm, "Work Democracy: Towards a Three-Dimensional Approach", Publication (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Creating a New Order of Things, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 63)
      Author: Alfred S. Warren, Jr.
  - Warren, Alfred S. Jr., "Creating a New Order of Things", Publication (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: A Presentation to the Board of Directors on GM Quality of Work Life, 1981; Publication (Box 26, Folder 64)
      Author: A.S. Warren, Jr.
  - Warren, A.S., Jr., A Presentation to the Board of Directors on GM Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Member Perspective on Health System Reform, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Washington Business Group on Health, "Member Perspective on Health System Reform", Publication (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: The Present and Future Problems in 'Japanese Quality Control' System, Publication (Box 26, Folder 66)
      Author: Yasutoshi Washio
  - Washio, Yasutoshi, "The Present and Future Problems in 'Japanese Quality Control' System", Publication (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 67)
      Author: Glenna Watson
  - Watson, Glenna, "Remarks", Publication (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Labor Targets the States, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 68)
      Author: David Warner
  - Watson, Jennifer, Furdell, Phyllis. "A More Promising Future- Strategies to Improve the Workplace", Publication (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: A More Promising Future- Strategies to Improve the Workplace, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 69)
      Author: Jennifer Watson and Phyllis Furdell
  - Watts, Glenn E., "The Future of Unionism and Work", Publication (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: The Future of Unionism and Work, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 70)
      Author: Glenn E. Watts
  - Watts, Glenn, "Unions and Quality of Work Life", Publication (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: Unions and Quality of Work Life, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 71)
      Author: Glenn Watts
  - Way, Philip K., "American Enterprise in a Time of Change: The Implications for Industrial Relations", Publication (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: American Enterprise in a Time of Change: The Implications for Industrial Relations, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 72)
      Author: Philip K. Way
  - Wayne, Sandy J., Ricky W. Griffin and Thomas S. Bateman, "Improving the Effectiveness of Quality Circles", Publication (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: Improving the Effectiveness of Quality Circles, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 73)
      Author: Sandy J. Wayne, Ricky W. Griffin and Thomas S. Bateman
  - "Ways to Get Stock on Your Company", Publication (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Ways to Get Stock in Your Company, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Weaver, Jerry, "Making American Industry Competitive Again: The Global Market Place", Publication (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: Making American Industry Competitive Again: The Global Market Place, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 75)
      Author: Jerry Weaver
  - Webb, Jervis C., "Managing the Race for Factory Automation", Publication (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Managing the Race for Factory Automation, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 76)
      Author: Jervis C. Webb
  - Weber, Arnold R., "Understanding Change in Industrial Relations: A Second Look", Publication (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: Understanding Change in Industrial Relations: A Second Look, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 77)
      Author: Arnold R. Weber
  - Weick, Karl; Wan Orden, Paul Organizing on A Global Scale: A Research and Teaching Agenda, Publication (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Organizing on a Global Scale: A Research and Teaching Agenda, 1990; Publication (Box 26, Folder 78)
      Author: Karl Weick and Paul Van Orden
  - Weikle, Roger D. and Hoyt N. Wheeler, "Unions and Technological Change: Attitudes of Local Labor Leaders", Publication (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Unions and Technological Change: Attitudes of Local Labor Leaders, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 79)
      Author: Roger D. Weikle and Hoyt N. Wheeler
  - Weill, David. "Enforcing OSHA: The Role of Labor Unions", Publication (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: Enforcing OSHA: The Role of Labor Unions, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 80)
      Author: David Weil
  - Weil, Reinhold, General Motors Corporation: Organization Development by Improving the Quality of Working Life, Publication (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: General Motors Corporation: Organisation Development by Improving the Quality of Working Life, 1981; Publication (Box 26, Folder 81)
      Author: Reinhold Weil
  - Weiler, Paul, The Future of Labor and Employment Law: Reflections on Wrongful Dismissal Within the Market, the Law and Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: The Future of Labor and Employment Law: Reflections on Wrongful Dismissal Within the Market, the Law and Collective Bargaining, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 82)
      Author: Paul Weiler
  - Weimer, George A., "Scanlon Plan Puts Everyone on the Team", Publication (Box 26, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: Scanlon Plan Puts Everyone on the Team, 1976; Publication (Box 26, Folder 83)
      Author: George A. Weimer
  - Weil, Paul C., "The Transformation of the American Workplace", Publication (Box 26, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: The Transformation of the American Workplace, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 84)
      Author: Paul C. Weiler
  - Wells, John Calhoun, "A Comparative Analysis of Joint Consultative Processes in the U.S.", Publication (Box 26, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: A Comparative Analysis of Joint Consultative Processess in the United States, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 85)
      Author: John Calhoun Wells
  - Weimer, William A., "Planning for Lifelong Education", Publication (Box 26, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Planning for Lifelong Education, 1988; Publication (Box 26, Folder 86)
      Author: William A. Weimer
  - Weinberg, Edgar, Highlights of Literature: Labor-Management Cooperation for Productivity, Publication (Box 26, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: Labor-Management Cooperation for Productivity, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 87)
      Author: Edgar Weinberg
  - Weinberg, Edgar, "Labor-Management Cooperation: A Report on Recent Initiatives", Publication (Box 26, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation: A Report on Recent Initiatives, 1976; Publication (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Weinstein, Marc, "Labor Relations at American Airlines Since 1983: A Case Study in Integration of Business Strategies and Human Resource Policies", Publication (Box 26, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations at American Airlines Since 1983: A Case Study in the Integration of Business Strategies and Human Resource Policies, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 89)
      Author: Marc Weinstein
  - Weinstein, Paul A., Issues in Bargaining Structure: The Case of Spain, prepared for the Mesa Redonda, Publication (Box 26, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: Issues in Bargaining Structure: The Case of Spain, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 90)
      Author: Paul A. Weinstein
  - Weiss, Andrew, "Simple Truths of Japanese Manufacturing", Publication (Box 26, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Simple Truths of Japanese Manufacturing, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 91)
      Author: Andrew Weiss
  - Weiss, Harvey and Richard L. Hill, "Counteracting the Stifling Effects of a Large Organization", Publication (Box 26, Folder 92)
    - Item 1: Counteracting the Stifling Effects of a Large Organization, 1984; Publication (Box 26, Folder 92)
      Author: Harvey Weiss and Richard L. Hill
  - Weiss, Richard M., "Will the Role of Managers Decline in the Corporation of the Future?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: Will the Role of Managers Decline in the Corporation of the Future?, 1988; Publication (Box 26, Folder 93)
      Author: Richard M. Weiss
  - Weitzman, Martin L. and Douglas L. Kruse, "Profit Sharing and Productivity", Publication (Box 26, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: Profit Sharing and Productivity, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 94)
      Author: Martin L. Weitzman and Douglas L. Kruse
  - Weitzman, Martin L., "Share Arrangements and Macroeconomics", Publication (Box 26, Folder 95)
    - Item 1: Share Arrangements and Macroeconomics, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 95)
      Author: Martin L. Weitzman
  - Welch, Joe L., Gordon, David, "Assessing the Impact of Flexitime on Productivity", Publication (Box 26, Folder 96)
    - Item 1: Assessing the Impact of Flexitime on Productivity, 1980; Publication (Box 26, Folder 96)
      Author: Joe L. Welch, David Gordon
  - Wellford, Hill B., JR. and Michael F. Marino, "Legal Aspects of No Growth and 'Downsizing'", Publication (Box 26, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: Legal Aspects of No Growth and Downsizing, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 97)
      Author: Hill B. Wellford and Michael F. Marino
  - Wells, John Calhoun, "Statement Before the Secretary of Labor's Commission on Workforce Quality and Labor Market Efficiency", Publication (Box 26, Folder 98)
    - Item 1: Statement Before the Secretary of Labor's Commission on Workforce Quality and Labor Market Efficiency, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Well, John Calhoun, "The Kentucky Experience", Publication (Box 26, Folder 99)
    - Item 1: The Kentucky Experience: State Government as a Partner in Labor-Management Relations, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Werneke, Diane, Microelectronics and Office Jobs: The Impact of the Chip on Women's Employment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 100)
    - Item 1: Microelectronics and Office Jobs: the Impact of the Chip on Women's Employment, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 100)
      Author: Diane Werneke
- Werther, William B. - Zwerdling, Daniel., Publication (Box 27)
  - Werther, William B., Jr., "Out of the Productivity Box", Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Out of the Productivity Box, 1982; Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Author: Williams B. Werther, Jr.
  - Wever, Kirsten Ruth, "Changing Union Structure and the Changing Structure of Unionization in the Post Deregulation Airline Industry", Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Changing Union Structure and the Changing Structure of Unionization in the Post-Deregulation Airline Industry, 1986; Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Author: Kirsten Ruth Wever
  - Wever, Kirsten R., Western Airlines and its Four Major Unions: ALPA, ATE, AFA, and the IAM, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Western Airlines and its Four Major Unions: ALPA, ATE, AFA, and the IAM, 1987; Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Author: Kirsten R. Wever
  - Wever, Kirsten R., "Toward a Structural Account of Union Participation in Management: The Case of Western Airlines", Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Toward a Structural Account of Union Participation in Management: The Case of Western Airlines, 1989; Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Beyond Productivity: The Quality of Worklife and the Adaptive Organization", Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Beyond Productivity: The Quality of Worklife and the Adaptive Organization, 1981; Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "What's Creating an 'Industrial Miracle' at Ford", Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: What's Creating an Industrial Miracle at Ford, 1984; Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Wheelwright, Steven C., "Building Excellence in Manufacturing", Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Building Excellence in Manufacturing, 1986; Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Author: Steven C. Wheelwright
  - Wheelwright, Steven C., "Japan: Where Operations are Really Strategic", Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Japan: Where Operations Are Really Strategic, 1981; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Whinston, Michael D., Collins, Scott C., Entry Contestability and Deregulated Airline Markets: An Event Study Analysis of People Express, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Entry, Contestability and Deregulated Airline Markets: An Event Study Analysis of People Express, 1990; Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Author: Michael D. Whinston, Scott C. Collins
  - White Collar Productivity Improvement Project, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: White Collar Productivity Improvement: Results of the American Productivty Center's Two-Year Action Research Project, 1986; Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - White House Conference on Productivity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Report of the Preparatory Conference on Capital Investment, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - White Conference on Productivity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Report of the Preparatory Conference on Government Organization and Operation and the Role of Government in the Economy, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Report on Preparatory Conference on Human Resources, St. Louis, June21-23, 1983, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Report of the Preparatory Conference on Human Resources, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Report on Preparatory Conference on Private Sector Initiatives, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Report of the Preparatory Conference on Private Sector Initiatives, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - White, G.C., "Technological change and the Content of Jobs", Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Technological Change and the Content of Jobs, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
      Author: G.C. White
  - White, G.C., Technological Changes and Employment: A Review of Some Implications for Company and Union Policy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Technological Changes and Employment: A Review of Some Implications for Company and Union Policy, 1982; Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - White, Geoff, "Effective and Satisfactory Work Systems: Notes on Some Important Features of their Design and Operation", Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Effective and Satisfactory Work Systems: Notes on Some Important Features of their Design and Operation, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
      Author: Geoff White
  - "A Program for the American Steel Industry, Its Workers and Communities", Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: A Program for the American Steel Industry, Its Workers and Communities, 1980; Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - White, Geoff, "Employee Involvement in Job Redesign", Publication (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement in Job Redesign, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - White, Geoff, Redesign of Work Organizations--Its Impact on Supervisors, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Redesign of Work Organisations- Its Impact on Supervisors, 1983; Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - White, Michael A. and Barrie L. Cooper, A Performance Measurement and Monetary Incentive System for Planners and Estimators at a Navy Public Works Center., Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: A Performance Measurement and Monetary Incentive System for Planners and Estimators at a Navy Public Works Center, 1986; Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
      Author: Michael A. White and Barrie L. Cooper
  - White, Michael A., Leanna Y. Atwater, and Deborah A. Mohl, A Practical Methodoly for Identifying Impediments to Productivity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: A Practical Methodology for Identifying Impediments to Productivity, 1981; Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
      Author: Michael A. White, Leanna Y. Atwater, and Deborah A. Mohl
  - Whitehead, Carlton J. and John D. Blair, "An Analytical Perspective on Quality Circles", Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: An Analytical Perspective on Quality Circles, 1982; Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
      Author: Carlton J. Whitehead and John D. Blair
  - Whitehill, Arthur M., Takezawa, Shin-ichi, "Workplace Harmony: Another Japanese 'Miracle'?", Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Workplace Harmony: Another Japanese 'Miracle'?, 1978; Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
      Author: Arthur M. Whitehill, Shin-ichi Takezawa
  - Whiting, Basil J., "Work, Family and Citizenship", Publication (Box 27, Folder 25)